{
    "subject": "resource/Kathryn_Cramer",
    "predicate": "ontology/genre",
    "object": "resource/Fantasy",
    "human_readable": "Kathryn Cramer's genre is Fantasy.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9159426093101501,
            "question": "Can you describe the typical themes found in Kathryn Cramer's fantasy works?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9065259695053101,
            "question": "What are some popular titles by Kathryn Cramer within the fantasy genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8487942218780518,
            "question": "Is Kathryn Cramer known for writing fantasy stories?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8329123258590698,
            "question": "What makes Kathryn Cramer's fantasy stories unique compared to other authors in the genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7763662934303284,
            "question": "Would you recommend Kathryn Cramer's books to someone who enjoys fantasy novels?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7687947154045105,
            "question": "Are there any recurring characters or settings in Kathryn Cramer's fantasy books?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5403788089752197,
            "question": "What genre of writing does Kathryn Cramer specialize in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4444437325000763,
            "question": "Which literary category is Kathryn Cramer's work primarily associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42155706882476807,
            "question": "Kathryn Cramer's writing often features elements of which fictional world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2995230257511139,
            "question": "What type of books does Kathryn Cramer write?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Kathryn Cramer's genre is Fantasy.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8501_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Kathryn Cramer's writing often features elements of which fictional world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8501_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which literary category is Kathryn Cramer's work primarily associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8501_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre of writing does Kathryn Cramer specialize in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8501_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8501_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8501_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8501_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8501_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8501_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8501_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8501_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8501_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8501_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8501_5.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The documents provide detailed information about Kathryn Cramer, including her profession as an editor and anthologist, and her work on various fantasy series such as Year's Best Fantasy."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that Kathryn Cramer is involved in editing and compiling anthologies focused on fantasy, such as the \"Year's Best Fantasy\" series. This supports the statement that her genre is Fantasy."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}